Motakabbir Hossan



m0takabbir@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/motakabbir



+8801316447745



https://portfolio.m0takabbir.live

Summary

I am an Engineering Student. I started Graphics design out of Curiosity now it became my passion.

I love to work with pixels. I have 3+ years of Graphic Design skills. I am very proficient at Photoshop and Illustrator. My Linkedin Profile also says that. This proficiency is built by the amount of time I invested in this sector.

I do Print-Design, Marketing & Advertising, Package & Product Design, Signage Design, Image Retouching, and also all kinds of Photo treatment.

I also have HTML, CSS knowledge with WordPress and JavaScript.

I believe these skills drove me to the right path that I have chosen.

Motakabbir

Experience



Intern

Glorious Bangladesh Aug 2021 - Present (1 month +) Creative Content Developer

Freelance Graphic Designer

Fiverr

Apr 2016 - Present (5 years 5 months +)

ဟု Freelance Graphic Designer

Upwork

Mar 2015 - Present (6 years 6 months +)

Freelance Graphic Designer

Freelancer.com

Apr 2016 - Present (5 years 5 months +)

Managing Director

Techsmsbd

Jan 2015 - Present (6 years 8 months +)

Education

Shyamoli Textile Engineering College

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics Engineering Jan 2020 - Aug 2024

National Ideal School & College

Higher Secondary School Certificate, Science Jun 2017 - Jul 2019

Janata Adarsha Bidyapith

ssc, Student Counseling and Personnel Services 2006 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

- First Step Korean Coursera 86PRXNUB5TB4
- Graphic Design Coursera
 6HL5U7LXHAE9
- Ultimate Adobe Photoshop CC Masterclass Udemy UC-dab692e2-c9c2-4757-be08-2dd292752e3f
- Graphic Design Masterclass Learn GREAT Design Udemy UC-193114dd-3e28-4f43-9e60-4117f135b217
- Introduction to Linux edX

2e488922c5fd4178b43f7611e0bfad2c

- Graphic Design Masterclass Intermediate: The Next Level Udemy UC-5768b92b-dcd7-4d73-b7e8-07ef4d98c912
- Graphic Design Bootcamp: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign Udemy UC-66b3920c-56c9-4172-ba80-509bf7b7e58e
- Adobe Photoshop CC Advanced Training Course Udemy UC-c86b307a-11fa-4ac8-9757-b5d565fcfd7d
- Adobe Illustrator CC Advanced Training Course Udemy

- Photoshop CC Retouching and Effects Masterclass by Chad Neuman Udemy UC-e0d63b2b-1c9e-4d32-840e-cb710b4ca41d
- The Beginner's Guide to Color Theory for Digital Artists Kurt Michael Russell -Udemy

UC-96edc526-ad8f-41de-8c35-53c59a93fd36

Skills

Adobe Photoshop • Adobe Illustrator • Graphic Design • Engineering • Web Development • Image Editing • Banners • Page Layout • HTML5 • Adobe InDesign

Honors & Awards



Oct 2015

Internet Genious - I-Gen

I was the champion at the District Level competition. This was about the Internet and the Digital Technology related Competition was held by I-Gen.